<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Organization XIII Database</string>
    <string name="organization_xiii_members">Organization XIII members</string>
    <string-array name="character_names">
        <item>Xemnas</item>
        <item>Xigbar</item>
        <item>Xaldin</item>
        <item>Vexen</item>
        <item>Lexaeus</item>
        <item>Zexion</item>
        <item>Saïx</item>
        <item>Axel</item>
        <item>Demyx</item>
        <item>Luxord</item>
        <item>Marluxia</item>
        <item>Larxene</item>
        <item>Roxas</item>
        <item>Xion</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="character_descriptions">
        <item>Xemnas, the Superior of the In-Between (狭間の指導者 Hazama no Shidōsha), sometimes referred to as the Superior or Lord Xemnas by members of the original Organization XIII, is the Nobody of Terra-Xehanort. He is the leader of the original Organization XIII, the former ruler of The World That Never Was, and a member of the real Organization XIII. Xemnas wields the power of "nothingness", which takes the form of non-elemental energy. In addition to expelling this energy in various forms, such as barriers and electricity-like arcs, he channels this energy into his weapons, red blades of energy called Ethereal Blades. He commands the Sorcerer Nobodies. Xemnas, as the Superior, is the founder of Organization XIII and has dominion over all other Nobodies. He is also the original Organization\'s most powerful member. Xemnas\'s name is derived from the alias his human form took when he assumed the identity of his exiled mentor, Ansem. Xemnas is a playable character in Kingdom Hearts 358/2 Days\'s Mission Mode.</item>
        <item>Xigbar, the Freeshooter (魔弾の射手 Madan no Shashu, lit. Magic Bullet Shooter), is the Nobody of Braig, the current vessel of the ancient Keyblade Master Luxu, Rank II within the original Organization XIII, and a member of the real Organization XIII. He is an antagonist in Kingdom Hearts II, Kingdom Hearts 358/2 Days, Kingdom Hearts 3D: Dream Drop Distance, and Kingdom Hearts III. Xigbar has power over space, and he uses this to freely redirect the projectiles fired from his twin Arrowguns, as well as to alter the battlefield. He commands the Sniper Nobodies. In Kingdom Hearts 358/2 Days, Xigbar is featured as a playable character in Mission Mode. In an interview, Tetsuya Nomura said that Xigbar\'s attacks have a high range, but he has slow reloading time.</item>
        <item>Xaldin, the Whirlwind Lancer (旋風の六槍 Senpū no Rokusō, lit. Six Lances of the Whirlwind), is the Nobody of Dilan and is Rank III within the original Organization XIII. He controls wind, and uses his power over the air to freely manipulate his six lances without holding them directly. He commands the Dragoon Nobodies, and has the second highest throne among the Organization. Xaldin appears in Kingdom Hearts II as a villain in Beast\'s Castle, and spends his time in the game attempting to plunge Beast into despair in the hopes of turning him into a Heartless and thus creating a Nobody. Xaldin is a playable character in Kingdom Hearts 358/2 Days\'s Mission Mode.</item>
        <item>Vexen, the Chilly Academic (いてつく学究 Itetsuku Gakkyū), is the Nobody of Even, Rank IV within the original Organization XIII and a reserve member of the real Organization XIII. He controls ice and uses it to command storms and blizzards, freezing his opponents solid, while defending himself with his massive shield. In Kingdom Hearts Chain of Memories, Vexen was the highest-ranking member of the Organization inside Castle Oblivion, but ironically he is the first Organization member to be eliminated. He creates the Riku Replica and uses the Replica to carry out several experiments on Riku and Sora. In Kingdom Hearts 358/2 Days, Vexen appears and he is also a playable character in Mission Mode.</item>
        <item>Lexaeus, the Silent Hero (静かなる豪傑 Shizuka-naru Gōketsu), is the Nobody of Aeleus and is Rank V within the original Organization XIII. His attribute is Earth, and he uses his massive Axe Sword, Skysplitter, to create earthquakes and punish opponents with devastating physical attacks. Lexaeus appears in Kingdom Hearts Chain of Memories during Riku\'s storyline, in which he works with Vexen and Zexion to manipulate Riku into serving them. In contrast to his fighting style and physique, Lexaeus is a disciplined schemer who often tries to keep people such as Vexen in line. Lexaeus appears in Kingdom Hearts 358/2 Days as a playable character in Mission Mode. Tetsuya Nomura has said that Lexaeus "has slow movement, but has very high attack power."</item>
        <item>Zexion, the Cloaked Schemer (影歩む策士 Kageayumu Sakushi, lit. Shadow-Walking Schemer), is the Nobody of Ienzo and Rank VI in the original Organization XIII. He is also an antagonist in Riku\'s storyline in Kingdom Hearts Chain of Memories. In battle, he weaves illusions to fight for him. Unlike the other Organization members, Zexion\'s weapon was originally unknown, and his talents were used only outside of normal combat. In Kingdom Hearts Re:Chain of Memories, Zexion\'s weapon was revealed to be a book called a Lexicon. Zexion appeared in Kingdom Hearts Chain of Memories as a participant in the struggle within the Organization between the newer and veteran members. He is also central to the plot to use Riku as a puppet in Castle Oblivion. Zexion also appears in Kingdom Hearts 358/2 Days, as one of the playable characters in Mission Mode.</item>
        <item>Saïx, the Luna Diviner (月に舞う魔人 Tsuki ni Mau Majin, lit. Demoniac Dancing in the Moon), is the Nobody of Isa, Rank VII within the original Organization XIII and a member of the real Organization XIII. He derives power from the moon and uses this power to enter a berserk rage where he mercilessly attacks opponents with his massive claymore. He commands the Berserker Nobodies. In the original Organization, Saïx serves as the second-in-command to Xemnas. Fittingly, Saïx is the second-to-last member of the first Organization to fall. Along with all other original Organization members in Kingdom Hearts 358/2 Days, Saïx is a playable character in Mission Mode.</item>
        <item>Axel, the Flurry of Dancing Flames (おどる火の風 Odoru Hi no Kaze), is the Nobody of Lea, and is Rank VIII within the original Organization XIII. He wields fire and enhances his weapons, twin chakrams, with his pyrokinesis to unleash powerful rapid attacks. He controls the Assassin Nobodies. In Kingdom Hearts Chain of Memories, Axel is the trump card for the rest of the organization, acting as a double agent in Castle Oblivion to keep track of Marluxia\'s plans. In Kingdom Hearts II, Axel betrays the Organization due to his friendship with Roxas, and acts of his own accord to aid Sora, though he had originally desired to turn Sora into a Heartless and restore Roxas. Axel appears in Kingdom Hearts 358/2 Days as a playable character in Mission Mode. Axel\'s human form, Lea, had been friends with Saïx\'s original persona, Isa.</item>
        <item>Demyx, the Melodious Nocturne (夜想のしらべ Yasō no Shirabe, lit. Nocturnal Melody), is Rank IX within the original Organization XIII and a reserve member of the real Organization XIII. He controls water, and uses his weapon, the sitar, as a musical instrument to make water fight for him in battle. He commands the Dancer Nobodies. In Kingdom Hearts II, Demyx plays a minor role where he is tasked with tracking down Sora to liberate Roxas\'s "true disposition". Although he dislikes fighting, he is directed to use "aggression" against Sora and his companions to bring out Roxas. In Kingdom Hearts 358/2 Days, Demyx appears and is also a playable character in Mission Mode.</item>
        <item>Luxord, the Gambler of Fate (運命を賭す者 Unmei o Tosumono), is Rank X within the original Organization XIII and a member of the real Organization XIII. He possesses the power of time manipulation and uses his ability to force his opponents to play timed games, with unfortunate consequences if they cannot learn the rules and lose. He commands the Gambler Nobodies. In Kingdom Hearts 358/2 Days, along with the rest of Organization XIII, Luxord appears in it and is also a playable character in Mission Mode. In Kingdom Hearts II, he harassed Sora and his friends in Port Royal, playing a game with them involving the cursed Aztec Treasure there. He later battles Sora alone in The World That Never Was, and is the third-to-last member of Organization XIII to fall. In Kingdom Hearts III, he returns as a member of the Real Organization XIII.</item>
        <item>Marluxia, the Graceful Assassin (優雅なる凶刃 Yūga-naru Kyōjin, lit. Graceful Assassin\'s Blade), is the Nobody of Lauriam, Rank XI within the original Organization XIII and a member of the real Organization XIII. As the lord of Castle Oblivion, he acts as the main antagonist of Sora\'s story in Kingdom Hearts Chain of Memories. He controls flowers, and he uses this attribute to command flower-themed minions to shoot beams of destructive energy, as well as to bombard the opponent with flurries of petals. Scythes are his weapon of choice and he commands the Reaper Nobodies. Originally discovered by senior Organization member Xigbar, Marluxia is the mastermind of an internal rebellion in the Organization against Xemnas, putting him at odds with fellow members Axel and Zexion. Marluxia makes an appearance in Kingdom Hearts 358/2 Days and is a playable character in Mission Mode.</item>
        <item>Larxene, the Savage Nymph (非情の妖姫 Hijō no Yōki, lit. Callous Vixen), is the Nobody of Elrena, Rank XII within the original Organization XIII and a member of the real Organization XIII. Larxene is one of only two female members of the Organization, and has a very sadistic nature. She controls lightning, and uses it to thrash opponents with rapid attacks while also attacking them with her weapons: electrified throwing knives. Ninja Nobodies serve under her command. She is one of the members stationed at Castle Oblivion during Kingdom Hearts Chain of Memories and is part of an internal struggle between the senior and rookie members. Larxene appears as a playable character in the non-canonical Mission Mode of Kingdom Hearts 358/2 Days and is the first playable female character in the series.</item>
        <item>Roxas, the Key of Destiny (めぐりあう鍵 Meguriau Kagi, lit. "Serendipitous Key"), is the Nobody of Sora and Rank XIII within the original Organization XIII, born when Sora took his own heart to restore Kairi\'s. Although Sora\'s heart was soon restored, Roxas continued to endure and exist, oblivious of Sora\'s existence for most of his life. He has the ability to use the Keyblade, and wields light, using it to direct rays that strike opponents with great power. He commands the Samurai Nobodies. Roxas was also one of the mysterious hooded figures in Another side, Another story… and Deep Dive. During the prologue of Kingdom Hearts II, the player controls Roxas until Sora is awakened. In Kingdom Hearts 358/2 Days, Roxas is the main protagonist. This game focuses on the time period between Roxas\'s birth and his departure from the Organization, eventually leading to his capture at the hands of Riku and DiZ.</item>
        <item>Xion is the Rank XIV member of the original Organization XIII as well as a member of the real Organization XIII. She debuted in Kingdom Hearts 358/2 Days as one of the game\'s main characters. She is not a normal Nobody and only a nominal member of the Organization. Because of this, she does not have a throne in Where Nothing Gathers, nor does she have a title or a type of Nobody to control. Instead, she is an imperfect replica created from Sora\'s leaked memories as a fail-safe in case both Sora and Roxas proved to be useless to Organization XIII\'s plans. Similar to Riku Replica, Xion was created by the Organization\'s scientist Vexen. While the nature of her existence enables her to use the Keyblade, Xion\'s existence also halts Sora\'s progression of regaining his memories to fully awaken while in his pod, something which Naminé, DiZ, and Riku recognize. As Sora\'s memories are the basis of her being, Xion initially looked like a hooded doll, but her physical appearance eventually changes depending on who is viewing her and who they have connections with. The majority of the time, she resembles Kairi, who was Sora\'s strongest memory at the time of her birth, though Xigbar sees her as Ventus, and Xemnas sees her as Sora. As Naminé stated while talking with Riku, Xion\'s face was originally blank, until Sora\'s memories found their way into Xion while she gained an identity.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="character_appearances">
        <item>Kingdom Hearts I Final Mix, Kingdom Hearts II, Kingdom Hearts II Final Mix, Kingdom Hearts 358/2 Days, Kingdom Hearts Birth by Sleep Final Mix, Kingdom Hearts 3D: Dream Drop Distance, Kingdom Hearts III, Kingdom Hearts III Re:Mind</item>
        <item>Kingdom Hearts II, Kingdom Hearts II Final Mix, Kingdom Hearts 358/2 Days, Kingdom Hearts Birth by Sleep, Kingdom Hearts Re:coded, Kingdom Hearts 3D: Dream Drop Distance, Kingdom Hearts X, Kingdom Hearts X Back Cover, Kingdom Hearts Union X, Kingdom Hearts III, Kingdom Hearts III Re:Mind, Kingdom Hearts Dark Road</item>
        <item>Kingdom Hearts II, Kingdom Hearts II Final Mix, Kingdom Hearts 358/2 Days, Kingdom Hearts Birth by Sleep, Kingdom Hearts 3D: Dream Drop Distance, Kingdom Hearts III, Kingdom Hearts III Re:Mind</item>
        <item>Kingdom Hearts Re:Chain of Memories, Kingdom Hearts II Final Mix, Kingdom Hearts 358/2 Days, Kingdom Hearts Birth by Sleep, Kingdom Hearts III, Kingdom Hearts Melody of Memory</item>
        <item>Kingdom Hearts Re:Chain of Memories, Kingdom Hearts II Final Mix, Kingdom Hearts 358/2 Days, Kingdom Hearts Birth by Sleep, Kingdom Hearts 3D: Dream Drop Distance, Kingdom Hearts III</item>
        <item>Kingdom Hearts Re:Chain of Memories, Kingdom Hearts II Final Mix, Kingdom Hearts 358/2 Days, Kingdom Hearts Birth by Sleep, Kingdom Hearts 3D: Dream Drop Distance, Kingdom Hearts III, Kingdom Hearts Melody of Memory</item>
        <item>Kingdom Hearts II, Kingdom Hearts II Final Mix, Kingdom Hearts 358/2 Days, Kingdom Hearts Birth by Sleep, Kingdom Hearts Re:coded, Kingdom Hearts 3D: Dream Drop Distance, Kingdom Hearts III, Kingdom Hearts III Re:Mind</item>
        <item>Kingdom Hearts Re:Chain of Memories, Kingdom Hearts II, Kingdom Hearts II Final Mix, Kingdom Hearts 358/2 Days, Kingdom Hearts Birth by Sleep, Kingdom Hearts Re:coded, Kingdom Hearts 3D: Dream Drop Distance, Kingdom Hearts III, Kingdom Hearts III Re:Mind</item>
        <item>Kingdom Hearts II, Kingdom Hearts II Final Mix, Kingdom Hearts 358/2 Days, Kingdom Hearts III, Kingdom Hearts III Re:Mind</item>
        <item>Kingdom Hearts II, Kingdom Hearts II Final Mix, Kingdom Hearts 358/2 Days, Kingdom Hearts III, Kingdom Hearts III Re:Mind</item>
        <item>Kingdom Hearts Re:Chain of Memories, Kingdom Hearts II Final Mix, Kingdom Hearts 358/2 Days, Kingdom Hearts Union X, Kingdom Hearts III</item>
        <item>Kingdom Hearts Re:Chain of Memories, Kingdom Hearts II Final Mix, Kingdom Hearts 358/2 Days, Kingdom Hearts Union X, Kingdom Hearts III</item>
        <item>Kingdom Hearts Re:Chain of Memories, Kingdom Hearts II, Kingdom Hearts II Final Mix, Kingdom Hearts 358/2 Days, Kingdom Hearts Re:coded, Kingdom Hearts 3D: Dream Drop Distance, Kingdom Hearts III, Kingdom Hearts III Re:Mind</item>
        <item>Kingdom Hearts 358/2 Days, Kingdom Hearts Re:coded, Kingdom Hearts 3D: Dream Drop Distance, Kingdom Hearts III, Kingdom Hearts III Re:Mind</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="character_images">
        <item>img_1</item>
        <item>img_2</item>
        <item>img_3</item>
        <item>img_4</item>
        <item>img_5</item>
        <item>img_6</item>
        <item>img_7</item>
        <item>img_8</item>
        <item>img_9</item>
        <item>img_10</item>
        <item>img_11</item>
        <item>img_12</item>
        <item>img_13</item>
        <item>img_14</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>